<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Metamorphosis</title>
    <link>https://robin-castellani.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Metamorphosis</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 23:58:22 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://robin-castellani.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>[from Florence import PyCon] Third day notes</title>
      <link>https://robin-castellani.github.io/posts/2024-05-25_pycon_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 23:58:22 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://robin-castellani.github.io/posts/2024-05-25_pycon_3/</guid>
      <description>[KEYNOTE] Myths and fairy tales around Python performance by Antonio Cuni - slides&#xA;Python is slow. Full stop. When optimizing a part of code, you could follow the Pareto principle: you can find that 20% of code which accounts for the 80% of total runtime, and then optimize that part. But then, after the optimization, you&amp;rsquo;ll find yourself with the remaining 80% of the code which now accounts for a big, not negligible part of the total runtime!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[from Florence import PyCon] Second day notes</title>
      <link>https://robin-castellani.github.io/posts/2024-05-24_pycon_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 21:25:38 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://robin-castellani.github.io/posts/2024-05-24_pycon_2/</guid>
      <description>[KEYNOTE] The attentive programmer by Daniele Procida - Canonical&#xA;Programming is the expression of will. We&amp;rsquo;re like God! 🌟&#xA;This is a love project, this is something Daniele has programmed about: C is for Camera. And this is something about writing the right content to the right audience: Diátaxis.&#xA;Poem&#xA;Pay attention Be astonished Tell about it&#xA;[TALK] Modern observability for Python by Adrian Garcia Badaracco&#xA;The way we monitor a Python program has passed through many layers: from print to logging, to metrics and traces, to distributed traces to Open Telemetry (OTEL).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[from Florence import PyCon] First day notes</title>
      <link>https://robin-castellani.github.io/posts/2024-05-23_pycon_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 15:21:18 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://robin-castellani.github.io/posts/2024-05-23_pycon_1/</guid>
      <description>[KEYNOTE] Mirror, mirror: LLMs and the illusion of humanity by Jodie Burchell&#xA;Blake Lemoine article on LamDA. 1984&amp;rsquo;s Newspeak: what&amp;rsquo;s the meaning of a word? Octopus thought test. Thomas Nagel&amp;rsquo;s paper: What is like to be a bat?.&#xA;Sources.&#xA;[TALK] Il software funzionante è il principale metro di misura di progresso by Raffaele Colace - 20tab srl (look at the Product Management Festival) The title is a citation of the Agile Manifesto.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[from Florence import PyCon] Public speaking workshop</title>
      <link>https://robin-castellani.github.io/posts/2024-05-22_pycon_public_speaking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 20:38:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://robin-castellani.github.io/posts/2024-05-22_pycon_public_speaking/</guid>
      <description>Public Speaking workshop with Lorenzo Barbieri lorenzo.barbieri@outlook.com&#xA;Tl;dr STOP putting an about me part in your presentation.&#xA;STOP boring your audience with useless information.&#xA;GIVE VALUE to your audience to make them happy and satisfied of hearing you speaking.&#xA;Full version Here you&amp;rsquo;ll find some advices for speaking in public. They&amp;rsquo;re particularly meant for sessions outside a company (for example at a conference), but they can be also applied to internal meeting in some cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My very first project (and how I won missing completely my goal)</title>
      <link>https://robin-castellani.github.io/posts/2022-08-02_story/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 20:35:56 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://robin-castellani.github.io/posts/2022-08-02_story/</guid>
      <description>This is a story into which you could find a bit of yourself, a story about a dream which turned into a different reality. Just let yourself enjoy the telling and dream your dream… 😉&#xA;It’s the roaring late 2000s. You’re a teenager, your parents give you an iMac because they think you could get fun out of it - and tinker with what they think is a cool tech platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello world 🗺️</title>
      <link>https://robin-castellani.github.io/posts/2022-06-22_intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 20:00:00 -0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://robin-castellani.github.io/posts/2022-06-22_intro/</guid>
      <description>As time passes by, we change and evolve to something new.&#xA;I decided to follow my dream. At least, the dream I’m dreaming on now. That is: travel and live in a warm place, where people are easy.&#xA;My short/medium-term strategy is creating a small blog along with a customized portfolio. I’ll have to learn a lot; I hope this little corner of the web will become useful to me and for those who are looking for the IT-part of myself.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
