<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Metamorphosis</title>
    <link>https://robin-castellani.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Metamorphosis</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 20:38:29 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://robin-castellani.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>[from Florence import PyCon] Public speaking workshop</title>
      <link>https://robin-castellani.github.io/posts/2024-05-22_pycon_public_speaking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 20:38:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://robin-castellani.github.io/posts/2024-05-22_pycon_public_speaking/</guid>
      <description>Public Speaking workshop with Lorenzo Barbieri lorenzo.barbieri@outlook.com&#xA;Tl;dr STOP putting an about me part in your presentation.&#xA;STOP boring your audience with useless information.&#xA;GIVE VALUE to your audience to make them happy and satisfied of hearing you speaking.&#xA;Full version Here you&amp;rsquo;ll find some advices for speaking in public. They&amp;rsquo;re particularly meant for sessions outside a company (for example at a conference), but they can be also applied to internal meeting in some cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My very first project (and how I won missing completely my goal)</title>
      <link>https://robin-castellani.github.io/posts/2022-08-02_story/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 20:35:56 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://robin-castellani.github.io/posts/2022-08-02_story/</guid>
      <description>This is a story into which you could find a bit of yourself, a story about a dream which turned into a different reality. Just let yourself enjoy the telling and dream your dream… 😉&#xA;It’s the roaring late 2000s. You’re a teenager, your parents give you an iMac because they think you could get fun out of it - and tinker with what they think is a cool tech platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello world 🗺️</title>
      <link>https://robin-castellani.github.io/posts/2022-06-22_intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 20:00:00 -0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://robin-castellani.github.io/posts/2022-06-22_intro/</guid>
      <description>As time passes by, we change and evolve to something new.&#xA;I decided to follow my dream. At least, the dream I’m dreaming on now. That is: travel and live in a warm place, where people are easy.&#xA;My short/medium-term strategy is creating a small blog along with a customized portfolio. I’ll have to learn a lot; I hope this little corner of the web will become useful to me and for those who are looking for the IT-part of myself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://robin-castellani.github.io/index-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://robin-castellani.github.io/index-about/</guid>
      <description>🦎 I&amp;rsquo;m not a lizard&amp;hellip; &amp;hellip; but I love the sun ☀️ and coding 👨‍💻&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m Robin and this is my little place in the metaweb! Here you&amp;rsquo;ll find something about me and what I like to do with the code.&#xA;Now living in Bel Paese (aka Italy), I dream to know more inspiring people, to travel and, who knows, to inspire someone.&#xA;Among my interests you&amp;rsquo;ll find anthropology, nature and climate change.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
